=Who Stole My Kiss=
= من سرق قبلتي =
=Episode 23=
= الحلقة 23 =
(Three months after) (Ultimate Kiss)
(بعد ثلاثة أشهر) (Ultimate Kiss)
Ultimate Kiss is online now!
Ultimate Kiss متصل الآن!
(Ultimate Kiss was officially online a month ago.)
(تم إطلاق Ultimate Kiss رسميًا على الإنترنت قبل شهر).
(Also, within three days,)
(أيضًا ، في غضون ثلاثة أيام ،)
(it's ranking number one among all the Otome games.)
(تحتل المرتبة الأولى بين جميع ألعاب Otome.)
(And I've been promoted as the team leader,)
(وقد تمت ترقيتي إلى منصب قائد الفريق ،)
(leading my team)
(يقود فريقي)
(in the making of Ultimate Kiss Two.)
(في صنع Ultimate Kiss Two.)
Hello, Lu Yuanyu.
مرحبا لو Yuanyu.
(Ting,)
(تينغ)
(the operation team told me that)
(قال لي فريق العملية)
(the players of Ultimate Kiss)
(لاعبي Ultimate Kiss)
(keep increasing tremendously.)
(استمر في الزيادة بشكل هائل.)
(Also, a lot of players)
(أيضًا ، الكثير من اللاعبين)
(are commenting down below the official account)
(يتم التعليق أسفل الحساب الرسمي)
(that not only they like the romantic scenes,)
(ليس فقط أنهم يحبون المشاهد الرومانسية ،)
they also like the character's expression of love
كما أنهم يحبون تعبير الشخصية عن الحب
after each level is completed.
بعد اكتمال كل مستوى.
Ting, you're amazing.
تينج ، أنت مدهش.
It's Valentine's Day today.
اليوم هو عيد الحب.
Did you call to
هل اتصلت بـ
flatter me?
تملقني؟
No way.
مستحيل.
Ting, how's your proposal coming along?
تينج ، كيف هو عرضك؟
You're now the creative team leader.
أنت الآن قائد الفريق الإبداعي.
Don't delay the script.
لا تؤخر النص.
I knew you called
عرفت أنك اتصلت
to tell me this.
ليقول لي هذا.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I'm already amending it.
أنا أقوم بتعديله بالفعل.
I'll send it to the group once it's done.
سأرسله إلى المجموعة بمجرد الانتهاء.
Okay, Ting. Bye.
حسنًا ، تينغ.  الوداع.
Happy Valentine's Day.
عيد حب سعيد.
(In the game,)
(في اللعبة،)
(I've made an open ending.)
(لقد قمت بعمل نهاية مفتوحة.)
(Even though the female protagonist knows who kissed her,)
(على الرغم من أن البطلة تعرف من قبلها ،)
(she didn't get together with anyone.)
(لم تجتمع مع أي شخص).
(I was worried that this will be disliked by the users,)
(كنت قلقًا من أن المستخدمين لن يكرهوا ذلك ،)
(but I didn't expect that they like this ending.)
(لكنني لم أتوقع أنهم يحبون هذه النهاية).
(They said this ending with regrets is beautiful.)
(قالوا هذه النهاية بالندم شيء جميل).
(But in the ending of the reality,)
(لكن في نهاية الواقع)
(regrets are regrets.)
(الندم والندم).
(I'll tell you a secret before I leave.)
(سأخبرك سراً قبل أن أغادر.)
(Actually, no one)
(في الواقع ، لا أحد)
(kissed you that day.)
(قبلتك في ذلك اليوم).
(You kissed Lu Bai by force.)
(لقد قبلت لو باي بالقوة.)
(I didn't expect that)
(لم أتوقع ذلك)
(it was just a mistake.)
(لقد كان مجرد خطأ).
(I've been looking for the person who kissed me.)
(كنت أبحث عن الشخص الذي قبلني).
(But actually, I kissed Lu Bai by force.)
(لكن في الواقع ، قبلت لو باي بالقوة).
(No wonder he didn't take the initiative to look for me.)
(لا عجب أنه لم يأخذ زمام المبادرة للبحث عني).
(It seems to him that)
(يبدو له)
(I'm just a playful girl)
(أنا مجرد فتاة مرحة)
(who flirts around.)
(من يغازل.)
(That's my story.)
(هذه قصتي.)
(I've never dated anyone before,)
(لم أواعد أي شخص من قبل ،)
(but I've kissed someone.)
(لكني قبلت شخصًا ما.)
(Twice.)
(مرتين.)
(I've made a lot of mistakes)
(لقد ارتكبت الكثير من الأخطاء)
(while looking for the person who kissed me.)
(أثناء البحث عن الشخص الذي قبلني).
(I've caused myself and others a lot of troubles.)
(لقد تسببت في الكثير من المتاعب لنفسي وللآخرين.)
(I've even lost my childhood friend.)
(حتى أنني فقدت صديق طفولتي).
(The most important thing is,)
(الشيء الأكثر أهمية هو،)
(I've spent too much time to realise)
(لقد قضيت الكثير من الوقت لأدرك)
(that the person I like is actually Lu Bai.)
(أن الشخص الذي أحبه هو في الواقع لو باي).
(By the way, Lu Bai likes me, too.)
(بالمناسبة ، لو باي يحبني أيضًا.)
(We've been having feelings for each other,)
(لدينا مشاعر لبعضنا البعض ،)
(but we didn't make it.)
(لكننا لم ننجح).
(Maybe we're not fated to be in love yet.)
(ربما لم نقدر أن نكون في حالة حب بعد).
(Although I feel helpless,)
(على الرغم من أنني أشعر بالعجز ،)
(I have a lot of great memories.)
(لدي الكثير من الذكريات الرائعة.)
(I'm very lucky)
(انا محظوظ جدا)
(that I've given my first kiss)
(لقد أعطيت أول قبلة لي)
(to someone I like.)
(لشخص أحبه.)
(Okay, let's not be so sad.)
(حسنًا ، لنكن حزينين جدًا.)
(My everyday life now is fulfilling.)
(حياتي اليومية الآن مُرضية).
(That's all I need.)
(هذا كل ما أحتاجه.)
(Li Xiaoxiao)
(لي شياوكسياو)
Hello, Xiaoxiao.
مرحبًا يا Xiaoxiao.
(Tingting, I'm seeing someone.)
(تينجتينج ، أرى شخصًا ما.)
What?
لما؟
(I didn't expect)
(لم أتوقع)
(I get to date someone I know from the Internet so quickly.)
(يمكنني تحديد موعد مع شخص أعرفه من الإنترنت بهذه السرعة.)
We're spending Valentine's Day together.
نحن نقضي عيد الحب معًا.
Aren't you neglecting your friend over your boyfriend?
ألا تتجاهل صديقك على صديقك؟
I'm rushing my script on Valentine's Day
أنا أستعجل نصي في يوم عيد الحب
and you're telling me that you're seeing someone.
وأنت تخبرني أنك ترى شخصًا ما.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Li Xiaoxiao.
لي شياوكسياو.
Hold on.
يتمسك.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Happy Valentine's Day, Ting.
عيد حب سعيد ، تينغ.
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
It's so heavy.
انها ثقيلة جدا.
It's Valentine's Day today.
اليوم هو عيد الحب.
Where's your girlfriend?
اين صديقتك الحميمه؟
Stop it right there.
توقف هناك.
Don't mention that.
لا تذكر ذلك.
I've broken up with her.
لقد انفصلت عنها.
All right.
حسنا.
I remember now.
أتذكر الآن.
My cute little assistant
مساعدتي الصغيرة اللطيفة
was teased by his girlfriend for being too old.
كان يضايقه صديقته لكونها كبيرة في السن.
You've broken up?
هل انفصلت؟
What comes around goes around.
ما يأتي حول يذهب حولها.
Cook for me now.
اطبخ لي الآن.
Yes, madam.
نعم سيدتي.
I'm going to cook!
أنا ذاهب لأطبخ!
Why are you back?
لماذا عدت
Don't even mention.
لا تذكر حتى.
The water in Bali is terrible.
المياه في بالي مروعة.
I can't stay there.
لا أستطيع البقاء هناك.
I come back to celebrate Valentine's Day with you, okay?
أعود للاحتفال بعيد الحب معك ، حسنًا؟
Some is here earlier than you.
البعض هنا أبكر منك.
You're here just to cook.
أنت هنا فقط لتطبخ.
Coming early doesn't mean everything.
المجيء مبكرًا لا يعني كل شيء.
How dare you fight against me, young boy?
كيف تجرؤ على القتال ضدي أيها الفتى؟
Young boy is cute.
الولد الصغير لطيف.
Ting, what do you think about
تينج ، ما رأيك
adopting a cute boy?
تبني ولد لطيف؟
Ting is having fructose intolerance.
تينج يعاني من عدم تحمل الفركتوز.
Also,
أيضًا،
a cute boy is not as good as a servant.
الولد اللطيف ليس جيدًا مثل الخادم.
I'm more shameless
أنا أكثر وقاحة
than you.
منك.
Right, Tingting?
صحيح ، تينجتينج؟
I can tell that
أستطيع أن أقول ذلك
you two are here to disgust me.
أنتما الاثنان هنا لإثارة اشمئزازي.
Am I still able to eat?
هل ما زلت قادرًا على تناول الطعام؟
We're really disgusting.
نحن حقًا مقرفون.
But you will never be disgusted
لكنك لن تشعر بالاشمئزاز أبدًا
by this person.
بواسطة هذا الشخص.
♪Does he like you?♪
♪ هل يحبك؟ ♪
♪Don't rush to interrupt♪
♪ لا تتسرع في المقاطعة ♪
♪You're being silent♪
♪ أنت صامت ♪
♪I lost the courage to talk♪
♪ فقدت الشجاعة للحديث ♪
♪That day was a suitable timing♪
كان ذلك اليوم هو التوقيت المناسب
♪I wanted to tell you♪
♪ أردت أن أخبرك ♪
♪Because you're gentle♪
♪ لأنك لطيف ♪
♪Like printed in my heart♪
♪ مثل المطبوع في قلبي ♪
♪Wanted to♪
♪ مطلوب
♪Embrace your breath♪
♪ احتضان أنفاسك ♪
♪Only you can♪
♪ أنت فقط تستطيع ♪
♪Solve the cute riddle♪
♪ حل اللغز اللطيف ♪
♪I like your♪
♪ أنا معجب بك ♪
♪Silly face♪
♪ وجه سخيف ♪
♪So happiness is always mentioned♪
♪ فدائما ما تذكر السعادة
♪It's in the bottom of my heart♪
♪ إنها في أعماق قلبي ♪
♪There are wind, rain and you♪
هناك رياح ومطر وأنت ♪
♪Every day♪
♪ كل يوم ♪
♪You've slowly become♪
♪ لقد أصبحت ببطء ♪
♪The best weather in my eyes♪
♪ أحلى طقس في عيني ♪
♪That day was a suitable timing♪
كان ذلك اليوم هو التوقيت المناسب
♪I wanted to tell you♪
♪ أردت أن أخبرك ♪
♪Because you're gentle♪
♪ لأنك لطيف ♪
♪Like printed in my heart♪
♪ مثل المطبوع في قلبي ♪
♪There are wind, rain and you♪
هناك رياح ومطر وأنت ♪
♪Every day♪
♪ كل يوم ♪
♪You've slowly become♪
♪ لقد أصبحت ببطء ♪
♪The best weather in my eyes♪
♪ أحلى طقس في عيني ♪
♪Holding me in your arms♪
أمسكني بين ذراعيك ♪
♪I like♪
♪ أحب ♪
♪Being with you♪
التواجد معك ♪